Finding Aid for William T. Gossett papers, 1927-1987
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Speeches, Articles, and Statements 1947-1981
  - [Untitled Speech], William T. Gossett Dinner (United Negro College Fund, Detroit, Michigan February 16, 1967 [Correspondence, draft] (Box 2)
    (2-65)
  - [Untitled Speech], Booker T. Washington Business Association Detroit, Michigan February 22, 1967 (Box 2)
    (2-66)
  - [Article about William Gossett], Michigan State Bar Journal February, 1967 [Drafts and correspondence] (Box 2)
    (2-67)
  - [Honorary Degree], Oakland University, Rochester, Michigan April 22, 1967 [Correspondence] (Box 2)
    (2-68)
  - "The Law: Leader or Laggard in Our Society," revised and published in Detroit Athletic Club News, April, 1967 (Box 2)
    (2-69)
  - [Missing Speech], Michigan Regional Conference on Crime Prevention, Oakland University, Rochester, Michigan June 8, 1967 [Correspondence and printed material] (Box 2)
    (2-70)
  - "In the Keeping of Lawyers," Commencement Address, Detroit College of Law, Detroit, Michigan June 12, 1967 (Box 2)
    (2-71)
  - "The American Bar Association: A Mission of Service," Minnesota State Bar Association Luncheon, Duluth, Minnesota June 22, 1967 (Box 2)
    (2-72)
  - [Untitled Speech], University of Pennsylvania Law School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania September 25, 1967 (Box 2)
    (2-73)
  - "Mobbism and Due Process," Conference of Judges of West Virginia, Parkersburg, W. Virginia October 20, 1967 [Draft, printed material, clippings] (Box 2)
    (2-74)
  - "Mobbism and Urban Progress," 73rd Conference of the Nations Municipal League, Milwaukee, Wisconsin November 14, 1967 [Draft, printed copy, correspondence] (Box 2)
    (2-75)
  - [Untitled Speech], Quarter Annual Meeting of the Chicago Bar Association, Chicago, Illinois November 21, 1967 [Correspondence, printed copies, printed material] (Box 2)
    (2-76)
  - "Statement to the Civil Rights Committee of the House of Representatives," (In behalf of the New Detroit Committee), Washington D.C. December 5, 1967 (Box 2)
    (2-77)
  - [Untitled Speech], Cincinnati Bar Association Dinner in honor of Murry Seasongood, Cincinnati, Ohio December 7, 1967 (Box 2)
    (2-78)
  - [Untitled Speech], (In behalf of the New Detroit Committee), Five o' Clock Forum, Detroit, Michigan December 11, 1967 (Box 2)
    (2-79)
  - [Untitled Speech], Association of American Law Schools, Detroit, Michigan December 28, 1967 [Draft and correspondence] (Box 2)
    (2-80)
  - "Electing the President: New Hope for an Old Ideal, " ABA Journal and Congressional Record, December, 1967-February, 1968 (Printed copies and correspondence) (Box 2)
    (2-81)
  - "Mobbism. vs. Urban Progress," Michigan Republican Seminar on Metropolitan Area Problems, Detroit, Michigan January 19-20, 1968 (Printed copy) (Box 3)
    (3-1)
  - [Introduction of Speech], National Association of Counties, Washington D.C. January 23, 1968 [Draft] (Box 3)
    (3-2)
  - [Untitled Speech], Genesee County Bar Association, Flint, Michigan January 26, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-3)
  - "Your Right to Say It," WGN-TV, Chicago, Illinois February 22, 1968 [Correspondence] (Box 3)
    (3-4)
  - Western States Bar Conference, Coronado, California February 23-24, 1968 (Printed material) (Box 3)
    (3-5)
  - "Balances and Controls in Private Policy and Decision Making," American Assembly on Law and the Changing Society, Chicago, Illinois March 14-17, 1968 (Printed copy) (Box 3)
    (3-6)
  - "Crime and Violence-Our Common Concern," National Association of Life Underwriters, Beverly Hills, California March 19, 1963 (Box 3)
    (3-7)
  - "Columbia Law School Forum, Columbia University, New York, New York March 28, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-8)
  - "The Michigan Challenge," State Chamber of Commerce March, 1968 [draft] (Box 3)
    (3-9)
  - [Untitled Speech], Stanford University School of Law, Palo Alto, California April 5, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-10)
  - "International Alumni Programs," Columbia in Detroit April 17, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-11)
  - [Untitled Speech], Arizona State Bar Meeting April 19, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-12)
  - [Untitled Speech], University of Missouri Law School Annual Dinner April 27, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-13)
  - [Untitled Speech], College of Law, University of Cincinnati April 30, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-14)
  - [Untitled Speech], Michigan State University Law Day, East Lansing, Michigan May 1, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-15)
  - "Only a Lawful Society Can Build a Better Society," Southwest Legal Foundation, Dallas, Texas May 3, 1968 [Draft and printed material] (Box 3)
    (3-16)
  - Kentucky State Bar Annual Convention, Louisville, Kentucky May 8-10, 1968 (Printed material) (Box 3)
    (3-17)
  - [Untitled Speech], American Bar Association and Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law, Washington D.C. May 20, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-18)
  - Untitled Speech], Annual Convention of the Florida Bar, Miami Beach, Florida May 24, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-19)
  - "The Best of Times-The Worst of Times," National Conference of Christians and Jews, Little Rock, Arkansas May 27, 1968 (Printed copy and material] (Box 3)
    (3-20)
  - Honorary Degree Award, Duke University, Durham, North Carolina June 3, 1968 (Printed material) (Box 3)
    (3-21)
  - [Untitled Speech] Tennessee Bar Association, Nashville, Tennessee June 6, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-22)
  - "Introduction of Orville Freeman," Western States Regional Meeting, American Bar Association, Denver, Colorado June 7, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-23)
  - [Untitled Speech], Dinner in Honor of the Judiciary, North Carolina Bar Association June 19, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-24)
  - Symposium on Private Investments Abroad, Southwestern Legal Foundation, Dallas, Texas June 20, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-25)
  - [Untitled Speech], Mississippi State Bar Annual Meeting, Biloxi, Mississippi June 28, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-26)
  - [Untitled Article], Symposium in memory of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Columbia Law Review, June 1968 (Photocopy) (Box 3)
    (3-27)
  - [Untitled Speech], General Assembly of the State Bar of Texas, Houston, Texas July 4, 1968 (final copy and printed material) (Box 3)
    (3-28)
  - "The Rule of Law," Brigham Young University Seminar Session, Valley Forge, Pennsylvania July 8, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-29)
  - "Mobbism and Due Process," Case and Comment, July-August, 1968 (Printed copy and correspondence) (Box 3)
    (3-30)
  - "Introduction-Legal Contrast Study," Committee on Education about Communism July 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-31)
  - [Untitled Speeches], ABA Annual Meeting, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania July 30-August 8, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-32)
  - [Untitled Speech], Missouri Bar Annual Meeting, St. Louis, Missouri September 5, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-33)
  - [Untitled Speech], Washington State Bar Association, Spokane, Washington September 6, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-34)
  - [Untitled Speech], Wyoming State Bar Association, Sheridan, Wyoming September 13, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-35)
  - [Untitled Speech], Mortgage Bankers Association of Michigan, Detroit, Michigan September 19, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-36)
  - [Untitled Speech], Citizens Research Council of Michigan September 20, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-37)
  - [Untitled Speech], State Bar of Michigan, Grand Rapids, Michigan September 26, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-38)
  - [Untitled Speech], State Bar of New Mexico, Roswell, New Mexico October 4, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-39)
  - [Untitled Speech], Second Sherwell Lecture at Marshall-Wythe School of Law, William and Mary October 10, 1968 (final copy and correspondence) (Box 3)
    (3-40)
  - "Where CLE Must Go to Be a Valid Educational Endeavor," 1968 National Conference on Continuing Legal Education, Chicago, Illinois, October 11, 1968 (copy and correspondence) (Box 3)
    (3-41)
  - [Untitled Speech], Legal Section, American Life Section, Chicago, Illinois October 14, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-42)
  - [Untitled Speech], 90th Anniversary of the Los Angeles County Bar Association October 23, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-43)
  - [Untitled Speech], Orange, San Bernardino, and Riverside County Bar Associations October 25, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-44)
  - [Untitled Speech], J.D. Degree Award Banquet, Drake University, Des Moines, Iowa October 26, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-45)
  - "Statement of William T. Gossett, "Before the National Commission on the Causes and Prevention of Violence, Washington D.C. October 30, 1968 (Printed copy and miscellaneous material) (Box 3)
    (3-46)
  - [Untitled Speech], Nebraska State Bar Association, Omaha, Nebraska November 7, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-47)
  - [Untitled Speech], Lawyers of Southwestern Michigan, Kalamazoo, Michigan November 13, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-48)
  - "In the Keeping of Lawyers," Yale Law Forum, New Haven, Connecticut November 18, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-49)
  - [Untitled Speech], Citizens Against Crime Conference of the National Council on Crime and Delinquency, New York City, New York November 22, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-50)
  - [Untitled Speech], Pre-Session Legislators Conference (sponsored by the Connecticut League of Women Voters), Hartford, Connecticut November 25, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-51)
  - [Untitled Speeches], Oklahoma Bar Association Annual Meeting, Tulsa, Oklahoma December 5-6, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-52)
  - "The Politics of Dissent," University of Michigan Winter Commencement, Ann Arbor, Michigan December 14, 1968 (Box 3)
    (3-53)
  - "Continuing Legal Education," American Bar Association Journal, February, 1969 (Printed copy) (Box 3)
    (3-54)
  - [Untitled Speech], New York State Bar Association, New York City, New York January 31, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-55)
  - "Justice and the Courts," National Emergency Conference of the National Council on Crime and Delinquency, San Francisco, California February 4, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-56)
  - [Untitled Speech], Bar Association of the District of Columbia, Washington D.C. February 12, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-57)
  - [Untitled Speech], Federal Bar Association of Detroit February 26, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-58)
  - "In the Keeping of Lawyers," Marquette University Student Bar Association, Milwaukee, Wisconsin February 27, 1969 (Printed copy and correspondence) (Box 3)
    (3-59)
  - [Untitled Speech], Detroit Rotary Club March 5, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-60)
  - [Untitled Speech], Alumni Dinner Villanova University Law School, Bala Cynwyd, Pennsylvania March 7, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-61)
  - [Untitled Speech], ABA-AMA Medicolegal Symposium, Las Vegas, Nevada March 14, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-62)
  - [Untitled Speech], University of Michigan Law School Honors Convocation April 5, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-63)
  - "Justice and Equality Depend Upon Law-and You!" Heidelberg, Germany April 15, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-64)
  - [Untitled Speech], Pennsylvania Citizens Conference on Judicial Selection, Second Series, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania April 28, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-65)
  - [Untitled Speech], Law Honors Banquet, Notre Dame Law School May 1, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-66)
  - "What Should the American People Do About the Electoral College?" Economic Club of Detroit May 5, 1969 (Printed copy and correspondence) (Box 3)
    (3-67)
  - "The Lawyer in Society Under Stress," Alumni Association Dinner, University of Chicago Law School May 8, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-68)
  - [Untitled Speech], Regional Seminar of the Public Relations Society of America, Wayne State University May 10, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-69)
  - "Bar Support for Organized Defender Services," National Defender Conference May 15, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-70)
  - [Untitled Speech], New Jersey State Bar Association, Atlantic City, New Jersey May 16, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-71)
  - "Social Security 1969 Rights and Remedies," ALI-ABA Course of Study, May 19, 1969 [Correspondence only] (Box 3)
    (3-72)
  - [Untitled Speech], American Civil Liberties Union Dinner, Detroit, Michigan May 25, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-73)
  - "4th of July," Drury College Commencement Address June 1, 1969 [Drafts and correspondence] (Box 3)
    (3-74)
  - ABA Statement on Campus Violence June 4, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-75)
  - [Untitled Speech], Sixth Annual Meeting of the State Bar of Georgia June 5, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-76)
  - [Untitled Speech], United States Conference of Mayors, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania June 17, 1969 (Box 3)
    (3-77)
  - [Untitled Speech], Minnesota State Bar Association June 19, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-1)
  - [Untitled Speech], Commencement Address at Cranbrook School, Bloomfield Hills, Michigan June 7, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-2)
  - [Untitled Speech], Yellowstone County Bar Association Dinner in honor of William J. Jameson June 11, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-3)
  - [Untitled Speech], Million Dollar Round Table, Hollywood, Florida June 21, 1969 (final copy and correspondence) (Box 4)
    (4-4)
  - [Untitled Speech], Quarterly Membership Meeting of the Philadelphia Bar Association June 24, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-5)
  - [Untitled Speech], Birmingham Rotary Club and the Exchange Club of Birmingham, Birmingham, Alabama June 25, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-6)
  - [Untitled Speech], First General Session of the Joint Utah-Idaho Bar Convention, Sun Valley, Idaho July 7, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-7)
  - "The Rule of Law or the Defiance of Law," American Bar Association Journal, September, 1969 Speech before the 92nd ABA Meeting, Dallas, Texas, August 11, 1969 [Drafts, printed copies, correspondence] (Box 4)
    (4-8)
  - [Untitled Speech], National Senate Delta Theta Phi Law Fraternity, Chicago, Illinois August 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-9)
  - [Untitled Speech], 51st Annual Meeting of the Canadian Bar Association, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada September 3, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-10)
  - Past President's Dinner, ABA Annual Meeting, St. Louis, Missouri August, 1970 (Box 4)
    (4-11)
  - [Untitled Speech], University of Utah College of Law, Salt Lake City, Utah October 6, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-12)
  - [Untitled Speech], Joint Luncheon of the Cleveland Bar Association and the Cuyahoga County Bar Association, Cleveland, Ohio October 20, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-13)
  - [Untitled Speech], XVI Conference of the Inter-American Bar Association, Caracus, Venezuela November 3, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-14)
  - "Presentation of Charles Evan Hughes Award of the National Conference of Christians and Jews to Chief Justice Earl Warren, Retired," Washington D.C. November 16, 1969 (Box 4)
    (4-15)
  - Oklahoma Hall of Fame Ceremonies, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma November 17, 1969 [Correspondence and clippings] (Box 4)
    (4-16)
  - [Untitled Speech], Senior Men's Club of Grosse Pointe April 14, 1970 (Box 4)
    (4-17)
  - [Untitled Speech], Commencement Exercises of University-Liggett School, Grosse Pointe Woods, Michigan June 10, 1970 (Box 4)
    (4-18)
  - [Untitled Speech], National Bar Association, New York City, New York July 22, 1970 (Box 4)
    (4-19)
  - "On Legal Aid Anniversaries," Fiftieth Anniversary of the American Bar Association's Involvement in Legal Aid Luncheon, St. Louis, Missouri August 11, 1970 (Drafts and printed copy) (Box 4)
    (4-20)
  - "Introduction of William James McGill, Economic Club of Detroit February 16, 1971 (Box 4)
    (4-21)
  - "The Best of Times-The Worst of Times, "Seattle-King County Bar Association April 30, 1971 (Printed copy, correspondence, miscellaneous material) (Box 4)
    (4-22)
  - [Untitled Speech], In presenting to the Crandall Library a portrait of Charles Evan Hughes, Glen Falls, New York May 22, 1971 (Box 4)
    (4-23)
  - "The Changing Criminal Justice System," Introduction of Former Governor of Delaware at the 79th National Conference on Government of the National Municipal League, Dallas, Texas November 16, 1973 (Box 4)
    (4-24)
  - Detroit Committee for Human Rights Day Observance, Silver Scroll Awards December 10, 1973 [Correspondence only] (Box 4)
    (4-25)
  - "Social Responsibilities of a Corporation Lawyer," Association of General Counsel October 14, 1974 (Box 4)
    (4-26)
  - "The Corporation Lawyer's Social Responsibilities ABA Journal, December, 1974 (Box 4)
    (4-27)
  - "Legal Counsel as a Social Adjuster," Harvard Business Review, May-June, 1975 (Printed copy) (Box 4)
    (4-28)
  - "Public Interest Law and the Legal Profession," December 9, 1975 (Box 4)
    (4-28a)
  - "Public Interest Law and the Legal Profession," Paul R. Trigg Testimonial Dinner, Phoenix, Arizona April 23, 1981 (Box 4)
    (4-29)
- Professional Activities
  Gossett's Professional Activities concern various legal committees and commissions on which he served and legal issues on which he had developed an expertise. Among numerous topics he dealt with as a member of the ABA and other legal organizations were business ethics, campus government and student dissent, electoral college reform, the International Court of Justice, judicial salaries, ABA meetings, the National Law Foundation, the National Legal Aid Defenders Association, fair trials and free press, and the education of lawyers. A second part of this series includes general office correspondence from 1958 to 1962 and files of correspondence for the American President's Life Insurance Company from 1965 to 1967.
  - Legal Topics and Committees
    - Business Ethics Advisory Committee
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - 1961 (Box 4)
          - 1962 (Box 4)
        - Department of Commerce 1961-1962, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Printed Material, General 1961-1962 (Box 4)
    - Commission on Campus Government and Student Dissent (CCGSD) and American Council of Education (ACE) Special Committee on Campus Government 1969-1970
      - Correspondence (CCGSD)
        - 1969 (Box 4)
        - January-June 1970 (Box 4)
        - July-December 1970 (Box 4)
        - 1971 (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
      - Correspondence (ACE) 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - Electoral College Reform
      - Correspondence
        - Commission on Electoral College Reform July 1966-April 1977, 3 folders (Box 5)
        - General January 1968-1975, 11 folders (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Material
        - Proposals
          - Senator Edward W. Brooke 1970 (Box 5)
          - Senator William B. Spong 1970 (Box 5)
        - General
          - Material on Voting Procedures for Direct, Popular Election of the President of the United States (Box 5)
          - Remarks by William T. Gossett (Box 5)
          - Brief Analysis of Certain Objections to Direct Election (Box 5)
          - Papers (Box 5)
          - Clippings (Box 5)
          - Printed Material (Box 5)
    - International Court of Justice
      - Committee for Effective Use of the International Court
        - Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 6)
        - Minutes 1962 (Box 6)
        - Papers 1960 (Box 6)
        - Printed Material 1960-1962 (Box 6)
    - Judicial Salaries
      - Federal Salary Commission
        - Correspondence (General) 1972-1976, 4 folders (Box 6)
        - Correspondence from judges April 1973-July 1973, 4 folders (Box 6)
        - Reports
          - Printed 1968, 1973 (Box 6)
          - Drafts 1973, 2 folders (Box 6)
        - Statistics 1946-1974 (Box 6)
      - Other Committees
        - ABA Executive Committee for Adequate Judicial Compensation 1975 (Box 6)
        - Coalition for Adequate Judicial Compensation 1976-1977 (Box 6)
        - Commission on Executive, Legislative, and Judicial Salaries 1969-1971 (Box 6)
        - Michigan State Officers Compensation Commission 1970 (Box 6)
    - Meetings, American. Bar Association
      - Mid-Year Correspondence 1974-1976, 3 folders (Box 6)
      - Annual 1974
        - House of Delegates
          - Amnesty (Box 6)
          - Annual Reports (Box 6)
          - Membership of Former Officers, 2 folders (Box 6)
          - Standing Committee on National Conference Groups (Box 6)
          - General (Box 6)
    - National Law Foundation proposals 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - National Legal Aid and Defenders Association
      - General
        - Reports 1951-1960 (Box 7)
        - Speeches 1955-1962 (Box 7)
        - Drafts (of pamphlets) 1962 (Box 7)
        - Printed Material 1961, undated (Box 7)
      - National Defender Project
        - Ford Foundation Grant Request 1964 (Box 7)
        - Annual Report 1964 (Box 7)
        - Printed Material 1966 (Box 7)
    - Section of Corporation, Banking, and Business Law, ABA, Correspondence 1961-1970 (Box 7)
    - Special Committee on Fair Trial and Free Press, Topical Files
      - Reardon Report 1968 (Box 7)
      - Reference Material 1968 (Box 7)
      - Miscellanea 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Special Committee on Professional Education, Correspondence 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Special Committee on Professional Relations and of the National Conference of Lawyers and Certified Public Accountants
      - Correspondence 1962-1968, 6 folders (Box 7)
      - Printed Material
        - "Background Articles, " 1965 (Box 7)
        - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Standing Committee on National Conference Groups Correspondence 1970-1974, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - General Correspondence
    - Daily Letter Books January 1958-September 1960 (Box 8)
    - Daily Letter Books October 1960-April 1962 (Box 9)
    - American President's Life Insurance Company, General Correspondence 1965-July 1967, 6 folders (Box 9)
- Topical Files
  A variety of legal and public service material comprise the Topical Files. Included are printed material and correspondence from the ABA, the Council on Legal Education for Professional Responsibility, the Council on Legal Education Opportunity (CLEO), and the International Juvenile Justice Standards Project. Additional files relate to the Legal Services Program, National Legal Aid and Defender Association, and the OEO National Advisory Committee.
  - William T. Gossett
    - Action for Legal Rights Inc. 1971-1973 (Box 10)
    - American Arbitration Association 1964-1977 (Box 10)
    - American Bar Association (ABA)
      - ABA News September 1967-August 1970 (some gaps), 3 folders (Box 10)
      - Commission on Law and the Economy 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Standing Committee on Legal Aid and Indigent Defendants 1979 (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1969-1978, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - American Bar Foundation Correspondence
      - 1974 (general) (Box 10)
      - 1976-1979 (The Fellows) (Box 10)
    - American Judicature Society 1964-1979 (Box 10)
    - Bellei, Aldo, Mario (Supreme Court Case) 1969 (Box 10)
    - Columbia University Law School Medal for Excellence 1974 (Box 10)
    - Consortium of Metropolitan Law Schools 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Committee for Diversity Jurisdiction 1971, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Conyers, John, Jr. and George W. Crockett, Jr. 1969 (Box 10)
    - Council for Advancement of Legal Education (CALE) 1970-1975 (Box 10)
    - Council on Legal Education for Professional Responsibility (CLEPR)
      - Correspondence 1968-1973, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Printed Material 1970-1972 (Box 10)
      - National Council on Legal Clinics 1961-1966 (Box 10)
    - Council on Legal Education Opportunity (CLEO) Correspondence 1967-1974, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr. (see Conyers, John, Jr.) (Box 10)
    - Detroit Bar Association 1978 (Box 10)
    - Douglas, William O. (see Fortas, Abe) (Box 10)
    - Fair Campaign Practices Commission (MI) 1974-1978 (Box 10)
    - FAIR Plan (Judicial Campaign Financing) Correspondence 1975-1979, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Federal Judicial Center, Ad Hoc Committee to consider 1967-1968 (Box 10)
    - Federal Trade Commission 1969 (Box 10)
    - Finch Law Day Award 1971 (Box 11)
    - Ford Foundation, Advisory Committee on Public Interest Law 1970-1980, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Fortas, Abe 1968 (Box 11)
    - Fortas, Abe, and William O. Douglas 1969 (Box 11)
    - Garrison, James (Clay Shaw conspiracy trial) 1969 (Box 11)
    - Genocide Convention 1970 (Box 11)
    - Gun Control legislation 1969 (Box 11)
    - Hart-Scott Anti-trust Bill 1975 (Box 11)
    - Haynesworth, Clement F., Jr. (Box 11)
    - Hughes, Charles Evan (lecture and article)
      - Correspondence 1973 (Box 11)